### Michal Przekop

#### contact

przekop.michal@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://mprzekop.github.io/Portfolio/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/micha%C5%82-przekop-994762188/

GitHub: https://github.com/MPrzekop

#### **Profile**

Unity generalist with experience working in small agile teams and developing for the Nintendo Switch system and PC. Lately, in my free time, I have been focusing more on a technical art aspect and tool making for the Unity engine, to see what can be achieved when you expand or replace solutions provided by Unity.

## Work experience

### Game Planet (July 2020 - Currently), Software Engineer

I worked on *Restaurant Renovation* - a casual "simulator" style Steam title, and provided systems for teams developing other titles.

- Gameplay: Developed character creator, modular first-person controller, skill system, player interactions, task system, and UI.
- Engine: Implemented real-time texture painting for stain/dirt removal, and serialization system.
- Tools: Provided systems and interfaces for authoring gameplay-ready assets and scenes.

# Gdansk University of Technology (October 2019 - January 2020), Lecturer

I gave lectures for high schoolers about 3D graphics and game development as a part of the "Akademia ETI" program.

### Creative Forge S.A. (June 2019 - September 2020), Designer, Software Engineer

I worked on the trailer and gameplay prototypes for the Far Fetched Steam game.

- Gameplay: Prototyped several iterations of a character controller that heavily focused on the character's movement feel and natural animation inertia.
- Graphics: Implemented a shader with a highly customizable lighting model. Created shaders for natural foliage movement and interactions. Developed customizable outline post-process.
- Engine: Provided optimized, interactive instanced particle system.
- Tools: Created tools for in-engine authoring grass and stone assets.

# Forever Entertainment S.A. (July 2018 - February 2019), Software Engineer

I worked mainly as a Unity Generalist on the *We are the Plague* title. Ported *Fly O'Clock* (Unity), *Grab Lab* (Unity) from mobile, and *Bad Dream Fever* (Game Maker 2), from PC to Nintendo Switch system. And helped to create a map import tool for *Rise Eterna*.

• Gameplay: Worked on player/team controller, inventory, and dialogue systems for a turn-based tactical RPG. Implemented local multiplayer for the *Fly O'Clock* port.

- Engine: Helped to implement and optimized AI and animation systems for a turn-based tactical RPG. Ported gameplay, UI, and input system, for the Nintendo Switch. Ported visual effects from Nintendo Switch to PC.
- Mentoring: Helped members of the internship program with bug fixing and Unity best practices.

### **Experience**

C#, C++, HLSL, Unity, Amplify Shader Editor, Shadergraph, Unity HDRP, Unity built-in pipeline, Git, Trello, Hacknplan

### **Education**

Bachelor of Science, computer science, Gdansk University of Technology (2015-2019)

### **Additional**

President of science club "Vertex" at GUT (October 2017 - June 2020)

I lead a science club that served as a platform for education and cooperation in game development, computer graphics, and virtual reality.